PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML5 & CSS3

JavaScript

TypeScript

Jasmine

React.js

Redux

Sass

Axios

Ant design

Bootstrap

Material UI

Node.js

Python

Django

Flask

Odoo PostgreSQL

PERSONAL SKILLS

Good communicator Reliable and professional Organized Good time management Team player Fast learner Self motivated

CONTACT

Country: Egypt

Phone: +201066702235
Email: aekhatean@gmail.com
Github: /aekhatean

∠
Linkedin: Adham Khatean

ADHAM KHATEAN

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Adham is a full-stack web developer with a passion for learning and experimenting with different technologies and tools. Professionally worked with JavaScript, TypeScript and Python.

Used popular front-end JS frameworks like Vue.js, React.js alongside with their ecosystem tools like Redux and vuex.

And back-end frameworks such as Django, and Flask.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER USING PYTHON INTERN Information Technology Institute - ITI | Nov 2021 - Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

Google Summer of Code | May 2020 - Sep 2020

- As part of my participation in Google Summer of Code 2020, I have worked at wikimedia foundation (wikipedia's umbrella foundation) on Wikimedia's TemplateData extension as an intern software engineer.
- My project was to allow Wikipedia editors to edit the "maps" object through a GUI instead of editing JSON in the core text editor.

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

VOLUNTEER

Shaket Dabos | Dec 2016 - Present

• Shaket Dabos was first started as an initiative to spread awareness about the importance of Blood donation, then it turned into a charity with the same main purpose but also helping people in other ways.

FUNDRAISER

TEDxDamanhour | Oct 2017 - Jul 2018

 As a fundraiser at TEDxDamanour my role was to ensure we secure enough fund to cover the expenses of organizing a proper TEDx event.

PROJECT MANAGEMENT COMMITTEE MEMBER Enactus Damanhour University | Oct 2017 - Apr 2018

 As a member of the project management committee at Enactus, my role with to cooperate with my colleagues in my committee, all the other commit, and independent individuals to come up with sustainable project idea that aligns with the UN's 17 sustainable development goals.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCES, MAJOR IN PHYSICS & MINOR IN CHEMISTRY Damanhour University | 2017 - 2021